Name	Short_description	Description	rxcode	first_paragraph	features	@image	sizes_dia	max_pressure	temp_range	operation	connection	material
 SED - KMA 495 Diaphragm Valve	Pneumatically operated Plastic Actuator and Stainless steel bonnet	Smooth surfaces, no explored nuts, no edges, and outside self-draining in all assembly, positions describe the optimised wash down design. The KMA series meets the highest demands of the pharmaceutical industry. Type 495 is availble in sizes DN 15 to DN 100 mm.	MBV	Romynox delivers KMA diaphragm valve series from SED for high purity applications in the pharmaceutical, food, fine chemical and cosmetic industries. The valve is predestined for applications with high purity, dirty and aggressive fluids, and gases.	Efficient plastic piston actuator with stainless steel distance piece RXBLLTControl air connection 90° to flow direction RXBLLTCDSA sealing concept RXBLLTFlexible diaphragm suspension RXBLLTEncapsulated diaphragm	/images/images/sed_diaphragm_valve_kma-495-15-25.jpg	MA 25 to MA 100	10	-20 Â°C to 150 Â°C	Actuator	Butt Weld, Flange, Tri-Clamp	316L (1.4435), Polyarylamide (Ixef)
SED - KMA 188 Diaphragm Valve	Pneumatically operated, plastic actuator directly mounted onto rvs body DN 8 - 20	Specialty of the KMD- series of SED is the plastic actuator. Compact design, the outside diameter of the actuator is the same size as the bonnet flange.	MAR	Romynox delivers the KMD series of SED Flow Control for high purity applications in the pharmaceutical, food, fine chemical and cosmetic industries. Specialty of the KMD- series of SED is the plastic actuator. Compact design, the outside diameter of the actuator is the same size as the bonnet flange.	Efficient plastic piston actuator direct assembled with the valve body RXBLLTControl air connectyion 90º to flow direction RXBLLTActuator high resistance to heat transfer RXBLLTSmooth exterior design ideal for wash downs RXBLLTEncapsulated diaphragm RXBLLTOptical indicator RXBLLTCDSA sealing concept	/images/images/sed_diaphragm_valve_kmd-188.jpg	MA 10 to MA 10	8	-20 Â°C to 150 Â°C	Actuator	Butt Weld, Flange, Tri-Clamp	316L (1.4435), Polyarylamide (Ixef)
SED - KMA 190 complete diaphragm valve	Pneumatically operated with Stainless Steel Bonnet and Plastic Actuator	"The KMA 190 is pneumatically operated and is used for sizes DN 4 to DN 15. The valve is predestined for applications with high purity, dirty and aggressive fluids, and gases. Smooth surfaces, no explored nuts, no edges, and outside self-draining in all assembly, positions describe the optimised wash down design.&nbsp;"	MAL	Romynox delivers KMA diaphragm valve series SED for high purity applications and meets the highest standards for the pharmaceutical, food, fine chemical and cosmetic industries.	Efficient plastic piston actuator with stainless steel distance piece RXBLLTDirection of control air connection is mountable in 90° rotations RXBLLTCDSA sealing concept RXBLLTFlexible diaphragm suspension RXBLLTOptical indicator	/images/images/sed_diaphragm_valve_kma-190.jpg	MA 8 to MA 8	8	-20 Â°C to 150 Â°C	Actuator	Butt Weld, Flange, Tri-Clamp	316L (1.4435), Polyarylamide (Ixef)
SED - KMA 195 SED Diaphragm Valve	Pneumatically operated and Stainless Steel Bonnet and Plastic Actuator - DN 8-20	The valve is predestined for applications with high purity, dirty and aggressive fluids, and gases. Smooth surfaces, no explored nuts, no edges, and outside self-draining in all assembly, positions describe the optimised wash down design. The KMA series meets the highest demands of the pharmaceutical industry.	MAP	Romynox delivers KMA diaphragm valve series SED for high purity applications in the pharmaceutical, food, fine chemical and cosmetic industries. The KMA 195 comes with a very compact design which makes it very suitable for T- and block valves.	Efficient plastic piston actuator with stainless steel distance piece RXBLLTControl air connection 90° to flow direction RXBLLTCompact design, the outside diameter of the actuator is the same size as the bonnet flange RXBLLTCDSA sealing concept RXBLLTFlexible diaphragm suspension RXBLLTEncapsulated diaphragm RXBLLTOptical indicator	/images/images/sed_diaphragm_valve_kma-195.jpg	MA 10 to MA 10	8	-20 Â°C to 150 Â°C	Actuator	Butt Weld, Flange, Tri-Clamp	316L (1.4435), Polyarylamide (Ixef)
SED - KMA 205 Manual Valve DN 4 - 15 mm	Manual actuated valve with stainless steel bonnet and plastic hand wheel	These valves are predestinated for applications with high purity, dirty or aggressive fluids and gases. Its smooth surface, without nuts or edges, combined with a self-draining exterior in all assembly positions, gives it an optimised design to be cleaned.	MBA	KMA 205 diaphragm valve serie form SED for high purity applications in the pharmaceutical, food, fine chemical and cosmetic industry. It reaches the highest demands of the pharmaceutical industry.	Stainless steel bonnet and plastic hand wheel RXBLLTManual actuated with rising hand wheel RXBLLTSealed bonnet with optical indicator RXBLLTAdjustable internal travel stop RXBLLTCDSA sealing concept RXBLLTFlexible diaphragm suspension RXBLLTSuitable for limited number of cycles of autoclaving RXBLLT 	/images/images/sed_diaphragm_valve_kma-205_s01.jpg	MA 8 to MA 8	10	-20 Â°C to 150 Â°C	Manual	Butt Weld, Flange, Orbital welding connection	316L (1.4435), Polyarylamide (Ixef)
SED - KMA 295 Manual Valve DN 8 - 20 mm	Manual actuated valve with stainless steel bonnet and plastic hand wheel	These valves are predestinated for applications with high purity, dirty or aggressive fluids and gases. Its smooth surface, without nuts or edges, combined with a self-draining exterior in all assembly positions, gives it an optimised design to be cleaned.	 MBC	KMA 295 SED Diaphragm valve for high purity applications in the pharmaceutical, food, fine chemical and cosmetic industries. The KMA series meets the highest demands of the pharmaceutical industry.	Stainless steel bonnet and plastic hand wheel RXBLLTManual actuated with rising hand wheel RXBLLTSealed bonnet with optical indicator RXBLLTAdjustable internal travel stop RXBLLTCDSA sealing concept RXBLLTFlexible diaphragm suspension RXBLLTSuitable for limited number of cycles of autoclaving	/images/images/sed_diaphragm_valve_kma-295.jpg	MA  to MA 10	10	-40 Â°C to 150 Â°C	Manual	Butt Weld, Flange, Tri-Clamp	316L (1.4435), Polyarylamide (Ixef)
SED - KMA 395 Manual Valve DN 15 - 50 mm	Pneumatically operated, Stainless Steel Bonnet and Plastic Actuator DN 15 - 50	Smooth surfaces, no explored nuts, no edges, and outside self-draining in all assembly, positions describe the optimised wash down design. The KMA series meets the highest demands of the pharmaceutical industry.	MBS	Romynox delivers KMA diaphragm valve series SED for high purity applications in the pharmaceutical, food, fine chemical and cosmetic industries. The valve is predestined for applications with high purity, dirty and aggressive fluids, and gases.	Plastic piston actuator with stainless steel distance piece RXBLLTCompact design RXBLLTControl air connection 90° to flow direction RXBLLTCDSA sealing concept RXBLLTFlexible diaphragm suspension RXBLLTEncapsulated diaphragm	/images/images/sed_diaphragm_valve_kma-395.jpg	MA 25 to MA 50	10	-20 Â°C to 150 Â°C	Actuator	Butt Weld, Flange, Tri-Clamp	316L (1.4435), Polyarylamide (Ixef)
SED - KMA 905 Diaphragm Valve	Manually operated valve with stainless steel bonnet and plastic hand wheel	These valves are predestined for applications with high purity, dirty or aggressive fluids and gases. Its smooth surface, without nuts or edges, combined with a self-draining exterior in all assembly positions, gives it an optimised design to be cleaned.The KMA 905 is standard provided with internal travel stop and stroke indicator.	MBF	KMA 905 SED diaphragm valve for high purity applications in the pharmaceutical, food, fine chemical and cosmetic industry. It reaches the highest demands of the pharmaceutical industry.	Stainless steel bonnet and plastic hand wheel RXBLLTManual actuated with rising hand wheel with optical indicator and stroke indicator RXBLLTSealed bonnet RXBLLTInternal travel stop RXBLLTLocking device RXBLLTCDSA sealing concept RXBLLTFlexible diaphragm suspension RXBLLTEncapsulated diaphragm RXBLLTSuitable for limited number of cycles of autoclaving	/images/images/sed_diaphragm_valve_kma-905.jpg	MA 25 to MA 50	10	-40 Â°C to 150 Â°C	Manual	Butt Weld, Flange, Tri-Clamp	316L (1.4435), Polyarylamide (Ixef)
SED - KMA 995 Diaphragm Valve	Manually operated valve with stainless steel bonnet and plastic handwheel	These valves are predestined for applications with high purity, dirty or aggressive fluids and gases. Its smooth surface, without nuts or edges, combined with a self-draining exterior in all assembly positions, gives it an optimised design to be cleaned.The KMA 995 is standard provided with a sealed manual actuator with an integrated optical indicator not disturbing the operation of the handwheel.	MBI	KMA 995 SED Diaphragm valve for high purity applications in the pharmaceutical, food, fine chemical and cosmetic industries. The KMA series meets the highest demands of the pharmaceutical industry. The design is following the GMP demands for sterile applications in consequent way.	Stainless steel bonnet and plastic hand wheel RXBLLTManual actuated with non-rising hand wheel with optical indicator and stroke indicator RXBLLTCDSA sealing concept RXBLLTFlexible diaphragm suspension RXBLLTEncapsulated diaphragm	/images/images/sed_kma_995_dn65-80.jpg	MA 80 to MA 100	10	-40 Â°C to 150 Â°C	Manual	Butt Weld, Flange, Tri-Clamp	316L (1.4435), Polyarylamide (Ixef)
SED - KMD 289 Diaphragm Valve	Manually operated valve with plastic bonnet and plastic hand wheel	Specialty of the KMD-serie is the plastic actuator, which leads to a very compact valve. The combination with the casted body makes this serie very interesting from a price point of view.	MAE	KMD 289 diaphragm valve from SED for high purity applications in the pharmaceutical, food, fine chemical and cosmetic industries.	Plastic bonnet and plastic hand wheel RXBLLTManual actuated with rising hand wheel RXBLLTSealed bonnet with optical indicator RXBLLTAdjustable internal travel stop RXBLLTCDSA sealing concept RXBLLTFlexible diaphragm suspension RXBLLTEncapsulated diaphragm	/images/images/sed_diaphragm_valve_kmd-289.jpg	MA 10 to MA 10	6	-20 Â°C to 150 Â°C	Manual	Butt Weld, Flange, Tri-Clamp	316L (1.4435), Polyarylamide (Ixef)
SED - KMD 385 Diaphragm Valve 	Pneumatically operated, Plastic piston actuator direct assembled onto the valve body	Specialty of this KMD-serie of SED is the plastic piston actuator which is directly assembled with the valve body, which makes it very compact and cost efficient.	MAY	Romynox delivers the KMD series of SED Flow Control for high purity applications in the pharmaceutical, food, fine chemical and cosmetic industries. 	Plastic diaphragm actuator, direct aseembled to the valve body RXBLLTActuator high restistance to heat transfer RXBLLTControl air connection 90° to flow direction RXBLLTCDSA sealing concept RXBLLTFlexible diaphragm suspension RXBLLTEncapsulated diaphragm	/images/images/sed_diaphragm_valve_kmd-385.jpg	MA 25 to MA 80	10	-20 Â°C to 150 Â°C	Actuator	Butt Weld, Flange, Tri-Clamp	316L (1.4435), Polyarylamide (Ixef)
SED - KMD 402 Diaphragm Valve 	Pneumaticalluy operated, Plastic piston actuator direct assembled onto the valve body		MAU	ROMYNOX delivers the KMD series of SED Flow Control for high purity applications in the pharmaceutical, food, fine chemical and cosmetic industries. Specialty of the KMD- series of SED is the plastic actuator. Compact design, the outside diameter of the actuator is the same size as the bonnet flange.	Plastic piston actuator  RXBLLTCompact design RXBLLTActuator high restistance to heat transfer RXBLLTControl air connection in flow direction RXBLLTCDSA sealing concept RXBLLTFlexible diaphragm suspension RXBLLTEncapsulated diaphragm RXBLLTSmooth exterior design, ideal for wash downs	/images/images/sed_diaphragm_valve_kmd-402.jpg	MA 25 to MA 50	10	-20 Â°C to 150 Â°C	Actuator	Butt Weld, Flange, Tri-Clamp	316L (1.4435), Polyarylamide (Ixef)
SED - KMD 982 Diaphragm Valve	Manually operated compact valve with plastic bonnet and hand wheel	This KMD 982 valve is characterized by its plastic bonnet and plastic hand wheel. It is standard equipped with a locking device. Locking device The locking device can be engaged by simply lifting the handwheel once the required position has been reached. To release the operating mechanism, simply return the handwheel to its previous position by pushing it downwards. When the system is in the locked position, u-lock can be installed to protect the plant against unwanted interference.	MAH	KMD 982 SED diaphragm valve for high purity applications in the pharmaceutical, food, fine chemical and cosmetic industries.	Plastic bonnet and hand wheel RXBLLTManual operated with a non rising hand wheel with optical indicator RXBLLTLocking device RXBLLTCDSA sealing concept RXBLLTFlexible diaphragm suspension RXBLLTEncapsulated diaphragm	/images/images/SED_diaphragm_valve_KMD-982.jpg	MA 25 to MA 50	10	-20 Â°C to 80 Â°C	Manual	Butt Weld, Flange, Tri-Clamp	316L (1.4435), Polyarylamide (Ixef)
SED - KMD 985 Diaphragm Valve	Manually operated compact valve with plastic bonnet and hand wheel	KMD is characterized by its plastic bonnet which comes with a compact design. In combination with a casting body it gives good value for money. The smaller sizes of the KMD 985 (DN15-DN50) are replaced by the KMD 982.	MAK	KMD 985 SED diaphragm valveÂ for high purity applications in the pharmaceutical, food, fine chemical and cosmetic industries. It comes in sizes DN 65, DN 80 and DN 100.	Plastic bonnet and hand wheel RXBLLTManual operated with a non rising hand wheel with optical indicator RXBLLTCDSA sealing concept RXBLLTFlexible diaphragm suspension RXBLLTEncapsulated diaphragm	/images/images/sed_diaphragm_valve_kmd-985-80.jpg	MA 80 to MA 100	8	-20 Â°C to 80 Â°C	Manual	Butt Weld, Flange, Tri-Clamp	316L (1.4435), Polyarylamide (Ixef)
SED - Multi block Diaphragm valves 	Compact multiblock with stainless steel diaphragm valves and stainless steel or plastic actuators	"By using SED multiblock the diaphragm valves design process circuits can be assembled from one block of stainless steel. Due to a minimal of contact makes the system faster. And cleaning is easier &nbsp;(CIP &ndash;SIP). With this design seal mass will be removed as much as possible. This will increase the heat absorption and the valve assembly quickly sterile (SIP). Technical Information&nbsp;"	MEA	Romynox delivers SED multi block diaphragm valves for high purity applications in the pharmaceutical, food, fine chemical and cosmetic industries. The SED multi block diaphragm valves includes the same features and performance of a standard 2-way diaphragm valve of the KMA and Steripur series.	compact  RXBLLTone block of stainless steel RXBLLTminimal surface contact RXBLLTfaster and easier cleaning (SIP-CIP)	/images/images/sed-multiport-valve-600x600.jpg	MA 	10	 Â°C to 150 Â°C	Actuator, Manual	Butt Weld, Tri-Clamp	316L (1.4435), Polyarylamide (Ixef)
SED - Steripur 206 Diaphragm Valve	Manual operated valve with stainless steel bonnet and hand wheel	These valves are predestinated for applications with high purity, dirty or aggressive fluids and gases. Its smooth surface, without nuts or edges, combined with a self-draining exterior in all assembly positions, gives it an optimised design to be cleaned.The Steripure is mostly used in conditions where diaphragm valves entirely made of stainless steel offer added value, such as cleanrooms or aggressive (corrosive) environments.	MAB	Steripur 206 SED diaphragm valve for high purity applications in the pharmaceutical, food, fine chemical and cosmetic industries.	Stainless steel bonnet and hand wheel RXBLLTManually actuated with rising hand wheel RXBLLTSealed bonnet with optical indicator RXBLLTAdjustable internal travel stop RXBLLTCDSA sealing concept RXBLLTFlexible diaphragm suspension RXBLLTAutoclavable	/images/images/sed_diaphragm_valve_steripur_206.jpg	MA  to MA 8	10	-40 Â°C to 150 Â°C	Manual	Butt Weld, Flange, Tri-Clamp	316L (1.4435)
SED - Steripur 217.25 Diaphragm Valves 	Pneumatical operated with Stainless steel Bonnet and Actuator	One advantages of this design are a longer diaphragm life time because there spring force is less. Other advantages of this design are a very high cycle life and a smaller overall dimensional height. Type 217.25 is also available in control functions fail safe open and double acting for standard working pressures. The valve is predestined for applications with high purity, dirty and aggressive fluids, and gases. Smooth surfaces, no explored nuts, no edges, and outside self-draining in all assembly, positions describe the optimised wash down design. The Steripur is used where diaphragm valves entirely of stainless steel add value, such as clean rooms or aggressive (corrosive) environment.	MAN	This valve is available in two different designs. The type 217.30 is available in the control function fail safe close (normally closed) and performs at a higher working pressure for standard application. The type 217.25 in control function fail safe close is mainly designed for filling applications or all other where the working pressure is lower.	High cycle stainless steel piston actuator RXBLLTCompact design RXBLLTLow control air volume, high switching speed RXBLLTHigh repeatablity RXBLLTControl air connection on the top RXBLLTDirection of control air connection is mountable in 90° rotations RXBLLTCDSA sealing concept RXBLLTFlexible diaphragm suspension RXBLLTClean and polished exterior design ideal for sterile wash downs	/images/images/sed_diaphragm_valve_steripur_207-25.jpg	MA 8 to MA 8	8	-20 Â°C to 150 Â°C	Actuator	Butt Weld, Flange, Tri-Clamp	316L (1.4435)
SED - Steripur 217.30 Diaphragm Valves	Pneumatically operated, Stainless steel Bonnet and Actuator	An advantage of the design is the longer diaphragm life time because the spring force is less. Other advantages are a very high cycle life and a smaller overall diemnsional height. The valve is predestined for applications with high purity, dirty and aggressive fluids, and gases. Smooth surfaces, no explored nuts, no edges, and outside self-draining in all assembly, positions describe the optimised wash down design. The Steripur is used where diaphragm valves entirely of stainless steel add value, such as clean rooms or aggressive (corrosive) environment.	MAN	This valve is available in two different designs. The type 217.30 in control function 'fail safe close', performs at a higher working pressure for standard applications. The type 207.25 in control function 'fail safe close' (normally closed) is mainly designed for filling applications or all other where the working pressure is lower.	High cycle stainless steeel piston actuator RXBLLTCompact design RXBLLTLow control air volume, high switching speed RXBLLTHigh repeatablity RXBLLTControl air connection on the top RXBLLTDirection of control air connection is mountable in 90° rotations RXBLLTCDSA sealing concept RXBLLTFlexible diaphragm suspension RXBLLTClean and polished exterior design ideal for sterile wash downs	/images/images/sed_diaphragm_valve_steripur_217-30.jpg	MA 8 to MA 8	8	-20 Â°C to 150 Â°C	Actuator	Butt Weld, Flange, Tri-Clamp	316L (1.4435)
SED - Steripur 317 Diaphragm valves 	Pneumatically operated with stainless steel Bonnet and Actuator - DN 8 - 20 mm	Smooth surfaces, no explored nuts, no edges, and outside self-draining in all assembly, positions describe the optimised wash down design. The Steripur serie is used where diaphragm valves entirely of stainless steel add value, such as clean rooms or aggressive (corrosive) environment. The Steripur 317 is the new version of the Steripur. 307 The technical data stayed the same. The 317 has the control air on the top, which makes it overall easier to install and to insulate the pipeline.	MAQ	"The Steripur 317, for use in sizes DN 8 - 20, has a compact design; the outside diameter of the actuator is the same size as the bonnet flange."	High cycle stainless steel piston actuator RXBLLTCompact design RXBLLTAdvantages in multiport bodies and manifold valve assemblie RXBLLTControl air connection is in flow direction RXBLLTCDSA sealing concept RXBLLTFlexible diaphragm suspension RXBLLTClean and polished exterior design ideal for sterile wash downs	/images/images/sed_diaphragm_valve_steripur_317.jpg	MA 10 to MA 10	8	-20 Â°C to 150 Â°C	Actuator	Butt Weld, Flange, Tri-Clamp	316L (1.4435)
SED - Steripur 397 Diaphragm Valve	Manual operated valve with stainless steel bonnet and hand wheel	These valves are predestinated for applications with high purity, dirty or aggressive fluids and gases. Its smooth surface, without nuts or edges, combined with a self-draining exterior in all assembly positions, gives it an optimised design to be cleaned.The Steripure is mostly used in conditions where diaphragm valves entirely made of stainless steel offer added value, such as cleanrooms or aggressive (corrosive) environments.	MAD	Steripur 397 SED Diaphragm valve for high purity applications in the pharmaceutical, food, fine chemical and cosmetic industries.	Sealed bonnet with optical indicator RXBLLTAdjustable internal travel stop RXBLLTCDSA sealing concept RXBLLTFlexible diaphragm suspension RXBLLTEncapsulated diaphragm RXBLLTAutoclavable	/images/images/sed_diaphragm_valve_steripur_397.jpg	MA  to MA 10	10	-20 Â°C to 150 Â°C	Manual	Butt Weld, Flange, Tri-Clamp	316L (1.4435)
SED - Steripur 407 Diaphragm valves 	Pneumatically operated, Stainless steel Actuator and Valve, DN 65 - 100	"Compact design, the outside diameter of the actuator is the same size as the bonnet flange. Smooth surfaces, no explored nuts, no edges, and outside self-draining in all assembly, positions describe the optimised wash down design.&nbsp;"	MXW	Romynox delivers Steripur diaphragm valve series SED for high purity applications in the pharmaceutical, food, fine chemical and cosmetic industries. The Steripur is used where diaphragm valves entirely of stainless steel add value, such as clean rooms or aggressive (corrosive) environment.	High cycle stainless steel piston actuator RXBLLTCompact design RXBLLTAdvantages in mulitport bodies and manifold valve assemblies RXBLLTControl air connection in flow direction RXBLLTCDSA sealing concept RXBLLTFlexible diaphragm suspension RXBLLTEncapsulated diaphragm RXBLLTClean and polished exterior design ideal for sterile wash downs	/images/images/sed_diaphragm_valve_steripur_407-dn80.jpg	MA 80 to MA 100	10	 Â°C	Actuator	Butt Weld, Flange, Tri-Clamp	316L (1.4435)
SED - Steripur 407-DN15-DN50 Diaphragm valve	Stainless steel bonnet and Actuator	Compact design, the outside diameter of the actuator is the same size as the bonnet flange. Smooth surfaces, no explored nuts, no edges, and outside self-draining in all assembly, positions describe the optimised wash down design. The Steripure is used where diaphragm valves entirely of stainless steel add value, such as clean rooms or aggressive (corrosive) environment.	MXW	The steripure diaphragm valve serie form SED for high purity applications in the pharmaceutical, food, fine chemical and cosmetic industry. It reaches the highest demands of the pharmaceutical industry.		/images/images/sed_diaphragm_valve_steripur_407.jpg	MA 	10	-20 Â°C to 150 Â°C	Actuator	Butt Weld, Flange, Tri-Clamp	316L (1.4435)
SED - Steripur 417 Diaphragm Valve 	Pneumatically operated, Stainless steel DN 15 - 50	Smooth surfaces, no explored nuts, no edges, and outside self-draining in all assemblies gives an optimised wash down design. The outside diameter of the actuator is the samen size as the bonnet flange. This gives advantages in multiport bodies and manifold valve assemblies. The Steripur 417 DN 15 - 50 mm is the new design of the former Steripur 407 DN 15 - 50 mm.	MAT	ROMYNOX delivers Steripur diaphragm valve series SED for high purity applications in the pharmaceutical, food, fine chemical and cosmetic industries. Compact design, the outside diameter of the actuator is the same size as the bonnet flange. The Steripur is used where diaphragm valves entirely of stainless steel add value, such as clean rooms or aggressive (corrosive) environment.	High cycle stainless steel piston actuator RXBLLTCompact design RXBLLTAdvantages in mulitport bodies and manifold valve assemblies RXBLLTControl air connection in flow direction RXBLLTCDSA sealing concept RXBLLTFlexible diaphragm suspension RXBLLTEncapsulated diaphragm RXBLLTClean and polished exterior design ideal for sterile wash downs	/images/images/sed_diaphragm_valve_steripur_417.jpg	MA 25 to MA 50	10	-20 Â°C to 150 Â°C	Actuator	Butt Weld, Flange, Tri-Clamp	316L (1.4435)
SED - Steripur 907 Diaphragm valve	Manually operated valve with stainless steel bonnet and hand wheel	These valves are predestined for applications with high purity, dirty or aggressive fluids and gases. Its smooth surface, without nuts or edges, combined with a self-draining exterior in all assembly positions, gives it an optimised design to be cleaned.The Steripure is mostly used in conditions where diaphragm valves entirely made of stainless steel offer added value, such as cleanrooms or aggressive (corrosive) environments.	MAG	Steripur 907 SED diaphragm valve for high purity applications in the pharmaceutical, food, fine chemical and cosmetic industries.	Manual actuated with rising hand wheel with optical indicator and stroke indicator RXBLLTSealed bonnet RXBLLTInternal travel stop RXBLLTLocking device RXBLLTCDSA sealing concept RXBLLTFlexible diaphragm suspension RXBLLTEncapsulated diaphragm RXBLLTSuitable for autoclave	/images/images/sed_diaphragm_valve_steripur_907.jpg	MA 25 to MA 50	10	-20 Â°C to 150 Â°C	Manual	Butt Weld, Flange, Tri-Clamp	316L (1.4435)
SED - Steripur 997 Diaphragm valve	Manually operated valve with stainless steel bonnet and handwheel	These valves are predestined for applications with high purity, dirty or aggressive fluids and gases. Its smooth surface, without nuts or edges, combined with a self-draining exterior in all assembly positions, gives it an optimised design to be cleaned.The Steripure is mostly used in conditions where diaphragm valves entirely made of stainless steel offer added value, such as cleanrooms or aggressive (corrosive) environments.	MXJ	Steripur 997 SED Diaphragm valve for high purity applications in the pharmaceutical, food, fine chemical and cosmetic industries.	Stainless steel bonnet and hand wheel RXBLLTManual actuated with non-rising handwheel with optical indicator RXBLLTSealed bonnet RXBLLTCDSA sealing concept RXBLLTFlexible diaphragm suspension RXBLLTEncapsulated diaphragm RXBLLTSuitable for autoclave	/images/images/sed_diaphragm_valve_steripur_997_100.jpg	MA 80 to MA 100	10	-20 Â°C to 150 Â°C	Manual	Butt Weld, Flange, Tri-Clamp	316L (1.4435)
SED - Tandem Diaphragm Valve 	Compact welded configuration of stainless steel diaphragm valves with stainless steel or plastic actuator	"Various configurations are possible; from simple tandem assemblies, where two valves are welded together, to very complex configurations of various diaphragm valves of different sizes, brought together in a cluster. Within SED there is strict quality control for every welded joint in the configuration. All accessible welds are polished to internal surface specifications. Then the configuration of the diaphragm valves is visually inspected and tested for maximum pressure. During the installation of welded diaphragm valve configurations, it is important to follow proper guidelines for the drainability of the diaphragm valve assemblies. &nbsp;"		These welded diaphragm valve configurations are specifically designed for processes in aseptic manufacturing plants, reducing dead leg in accordance with cGMP.		/images/images/sed-sa11h_188-600x600.jpg	MA 	10	 Â°C to 150 Â°C	Actuator, Manual	Butt Weld, Tri-Clamp	316L (1.4435), Polyarylamide (Ixef)
SED - Tank Bottom Diaphragm Valve Customized designs	Compact stainless steel tank bottom valves	"The SED tank bottom valve incorporates the same features and performanceof a standard 2-way diaphragm valve from the KMA and Steripure series utilizing the same valve components for a flush mounted tank bottom valve or side mounted tank and sample valve.&nbsp;The SED tank bottom diaphragm valves with a casting body are unique and very affordable. The datasheet (see below) shows some examples of standard and customized designs of tank diaphragm valves."		The SED Tank Bottom Valve is designed for applications in the aseptic process industry offering a pocket-free interior surface, eliminating entrapment areas and minimizing flow resistance thus reducing the potential for process contamination.	The tank valve body is machined as standard from solid bar stock material 1.4435/316L RXBLLTThe standard design offers one valve port outlet RXBLLTMinimized dead leg and internal sump RXBLLTSuitable for mounting with SED Steripur and KMA series Actuated	/images/images/sed-495-tank-bottom-valve-600x600.jpg	MA 8 to MA 100	10	 Â°C	Actuator, Manual	Butt Weld, Tri-Clamp	316L (1.4435), Polyarylamide (Ixef)
SED - ZDL T-valve Zero Dead Leg Diaphragm Valve 	T-diaphragm valve ZDL with stainless steel or plastic actuator	The zero dead leg diaphragm valves are usually used as a point of use in a WFI loop system. It can also be used as a drain point in other systems. The actuators for valves ZDL are part of the KMA or Steripur Series of SED. The SED T-diaphragm valves are also available with a casting body. This is an unique product of SED.		ROMYNOX delivers the T-valve, with zero dead leg, of SED for high purity applications in the pharmaceutical, food, fine chemical and cosmetic industries.	 <strong>Features</strong> Customer?s specific design RXBLLTCompact design and smaller envelope dimension is achievable with the Steripur Series actuators RXBLLTCombination of many different nominal diameters RXBLLTOptimized drainability RXBLLTMinimized dead leg RXBLLTReduces surface contact, hold up volume and cross contamination of the product RXBLLTReduction of fittings, tubing and field welds in the system RXBLLTReduces qualification and validation documentation requirements RXBLLTAll end connections and materials are available according to the customer?s specification	/images/images/typ-995-zero-dead-leg-600x600.jpg	MA 	10	 Â°C to 150 Â°C	Actuator, Manual	Butt Weld, Tri-Clamp	316L (1.4435)
SED Chromatography Diaphragm Valve	Compact stainless steel diaphragm chromatography valve	"The SED chromatography diaphragm valves design can be assembled from one block of stainless steel. Due to a minimal of contact makes the system faster. And cleaning is easier (CIP&ndash;SIP). With this design seal mass will be removed as much as possible. This will increase the heat absorption and the valve assembly quickly sterile (SIP). There are valves with or without bypass."		ROMYNOX delivers SED chromatography diaphragm valves for high purity applications in the pharmaceutical, food, fine chemical and cosmetic industries. The SED chromatography diaphragm valves includes the same features and performance of a standard 2-way diaphragm valve of the KMA and Steripur series.		/images/images/sed_chromatography.jpg	MA 8 to MA 100	10	 Â°C to 160 Â°C	Actuator, Manual	Butt Weld, Tri-Clamp	316L (1.4435)
Steripur 207-25 SED Diaphragm valve	Stainless steel bonnet and Actuator	This valve is available in two different designs. The type 207.30 is available in the control function fail safe close and performs at a higher working pressure for standard application. The type 207.25 in control function fail safe close is mainly designed for filling applications or all other where the working pressure is lower. One advantages of this design are a longer diaphragm life time because there spring force is less. Other advantages of this design are a very high cycle life and a smaller overall dimensional height. Type 207.25 is also available in control functions fail safe open and double acting for standard working pressures.The valve is predestined for applications with high purity, dirty and aggressive fluids, and gases. Smooth surfaces, no explored nuts, no edges, and outside self-draining in all assembly, positions describe the optimised wash down design. The Steripure is used where diaphragm valves entirely of stainless steel add value, such as clean rooms or aggressive (corrosive) environment.		The steripure diaphragm valve serie form SED for high purity applications in the pharmaceutical, food, fine chemical and cosmetic industry. It reaches the highest demands of the pharmaceutical industry		/images/images/sed_diaphragm_valve_steripur_207-25.jpg	MA 	45	-20 Â°C to 150 Â°C	Actuator	Butt Weld, Flange, Tri-Clamp	316L (1.4435)
Steripur 207-30 SED Diaphragm valve	Stainless steel bonnet and Actuator	High cycle stainless steel piston actuator with double piston.The valve is predestined for applications with high purity, dirty and aggressive fluids, and gases. Smooth surfaces, no explored nuts, no edges, and outside self-draining in all assembly, positions describe the optimised wash down design. The Steripure is used where diaphragm valves entirely of stainless steel add value, such as clean rooms or aggressive (corrosive) environment.		This valve is available in two different designs. The type 207.30 is available in the control function fail safe close and performs at a higher working pressure for standard application. The type 207.25 in control function fail safe close is mainly designed for filling applications or all other where the working pressure is lower.		/images/images/sed_diaphragm_valve_steripur_207-30.jpg	MA 	8	-20 Â°C to 150 Â°C	Actuator	Butt Weld, Flange, Tri-Clamp	316L (1.4404)
Steripur 307 SED Diaphragm valve DELETE	Stainless steel bonnet and Actuator	Compact design, the outside diameter of the actuator is the same size as the bonnet flange. Smooth surfaces, no explored nuts, no edges, and outside self-draining in all assembly, positions describe the optimised wash down design. The Steripure is used where diaphragm valves entirely of stainless steel add value, such as clean rooms or aggressive (corrosive) environment.		The steripure diaphragm valve serie form SED for high purity applications in the pharmaceutical, food, fine chemical and cosmetic industry. It reaches the highest demands of the pharmaceutical industry		/images/images/sed_diaphragm_valve_steripur_307.jpg	MA 	8	-20 Â°C to 150 Â°C	Actuator	Butt Weld, Flange, Tri-Clamp	316L (1.4435)
Twin SED Diaphragm Valve 	Ideal for filling bottles or barrels			"The Twin Diaphragm Valve combines two diaphragm valve bodies in one valve block assembled with two pneumautically operated diaphragm valve actuators. The twin diaphragm valve has one inlet and one outlet tube end. The valve actuators can be operated independently from each other and optionally are different control components available to visualize and control the process.

"	Economical filling valve RXBLLTHigh cycle lifetime RXBLLTControl air connection in or 90° to flow direction RXBLLTCDSA sealing concept, easy to clean RXBLLTCompact solution RXBLLTLow weight RXBLLTOptimized internal design for maximum flow rate RXBLLTLess welding RXBLLTHigh filling volume RXBLLTMaterial 1.4435/316L solid block and investment cast RXBLLTEncapsulated Diaphragm RXBLLTSmooth exterior design ideal for wash down RXBLLTAvailable with a wide range of Control equipment and<br />accessories. RXBLLTAll actuator series suitable	/images/images/sed_twin_diaphragm_valve_for_filling.jpg	MA 	8	 Â°C	Actuator	Butt Weld, Flange, Tri-Clamp	316L (1.4435)
